I am Chipanthenga and I am a village headman.
I'm speaking about water issues as we are at the river.
I am surounded by four villages, namely,
Mayola, Julious, Amndinda, and Chiyani.
We have been struggling with dirty water for a long time.
We came from Lilongwe to settle in these villages
in Kasungu in 1976.
The water challenges in my villages never end. We have
tried to raise our concerns for a long time.
Men from all the villages are still escorting their wives to
the river, protecting them from wild animals.
We are requesting help if possible. We are looking for
organizations that understand the problems we are facing.
They have to help my community. The major problem in my
villages is safe water.
As we speak women are not sleeping because they are fetching
water.
We have tried to reach out our counselor and our
Member of Parliment to explain our problems.