Bridges To Malawi fight against hunger in Malawi
Maize distribution planning
My name is Kampiyoni Mwale and I stay at wimbe village
I am a commitee member. What has happened today is great
I thank you Minjale and BTM for this maize support and We
will live healthy lives
Bridges To Malawi fight against hunger in Malawi
My name is Mphezewa Banda. I am the coordinator of Kadifula
Aids Support Group
I want to thank K2 TASO and BTM for the food support you
have delivered
The truth is that were sleeping empty stomachs
Sometimes we were eating mangoes
With the coming of this Maize, this means that today we will
eat  and from here I will go straight to the Maize mill
Thank  you very much for this Maize support
Bridges To Malawi has donated maize to 14,721 People in the
parts of Kasungu district in Malawi
Encouraging the support group members to be active in all
activities
I thank Bridges To Malawi for this Maize support
My name is Lyness Chirwa. I stay at kanyumba village and I
am a member of Kapyanga Aids support group
When I heard that we will receive Maize today,I am thankful
We are eating banana roots as you can see and this Maize
support must continue
I thank K2 TASO and Bridges To Malawi for this donation
Thank you
Maize distribution team arriving at Kapyanga community
Please donate to Bridges To Malawi to save lives
https:bridgestomalawi.org
Camera and Editor: Sikayenera Chiwengo